LEONARD: Okay, we've got power to the laser.
Le laser est branché.
lshould've brought an umbrella.
J‘aurais dû amener un parapluie.
-What for? It's not gonna rain. -I know.
- Il ne va pas pleuvoir. - Je sais.
But with skin as fair as mine, moon burn is a real possibility.
Mais avec une peau comme la mienne, un coup de lune est à craindre.
That's a buzzinga, right?
C'est une blague ?
One of my best, don't you think?
Une de mes meilleures, non ?
Howard, double-check the equatorial mount on the laser.
Vérifie la monture équatoriale du laser.
-Need it locked on the Sea of Tranquility. -You got it.
- Bloque-Ie sur la Mer dela Tranquillité. - D‘accord.
Raj, no.
Ra], non.
Billions of dollars have gone into inventing the Internet...
Internet et les photos de femmes nues
...and filling it with pictures of naked women...
ont été créés pour que tu n'aies pas àjouer au voyeur.
It's not like that. I'm watching someone's TV.
Mais non. Je regarde la télé :
The Good Wife is on.
The Good Wife.
I tell you, this is my new Grey's Anatomy.
C‘est ce qui va remplacer Grey‘s Anatomy.
Leonard, what is that? What is that?
Leonard, c‘est quoi ça ?
Relax, it's just a dirty sock.
Relaxe, une chaussette sale.
How on earth can you say "dirty sock" and "relax" in the same sentence?
Relaxe et chaussette sale, tu trouves ça compatible ?
Sheldon, the world is filled with dirty, discarded socks.
Le monde est rempli de chaussettes sales.
Not my world.
Pas le mien.
You know who'd really dig seeing this experiment? Penny.
Penny aurait adoré suivre cette expérience.
I wasn't aware that lunar ranging was her thing.
Elle s‘intéresserait aux réflecteurs lunaires ?
Although I suppose...
Quoique,
...the retroreflector left on the moon by Neil Armstrong...
Ie rétroréflecteur laissé par Armstrong
...does qualify as a shiny object.
est en effet un objet brillant.
Ask her to come up.
Dis—lui de monter.
I don't know. It's still weird since, you know....
Je ne sais pas. C‘est bizarre depuis...
-She dumped you? -She didn't dump me.
- Qu'elle t‘a largué ? - Non.
We were just in different places in the relationship.
On n'allait pas dans la même direction.
I fail to see how a relationship...
Je n‘avais pas remarqué
...can have the qualities of a geographic location.
le côté géographique d‘une relation.
Well, it's very simple. Leonard was living in a town called Please Don't Leave Me...
C‘est très simple. Leonard vivait à Ne Me Laisse Pas,
...while Penny had just moved to the island of Bye-bye.
alors que Penny venait d‘emménager à Bye Bye Island.
Screw you, guys. I'm gonna go see if she's home.
Je vais voir si elle est la.
If it's not too much trouble, I'd like to point this at the moon now.
Ça t'ennuierait beaucoup de pointer ça vers la lune ?
Wait a second. The good wife is crying.
Attends une seconde, elle pleure.
Something's very wrong.
Il y a un probléme.
Oh, hi. What's going on?
Qu'y a-t-il ?
We're up on the roof bouncing laser beams off the moon.
On va faire rebondir un laser sur la lune.
I'm sorry, what?
Pardon, quoi ?
It's cool. We've got a two-meter parabolic reflector and everything.
On a récupéré un réflecteur parabolique de 2 M.
-I thought you might wanna see it. -That makes no sense.
- Tu voudrais le voir ? - lllogique.
How can you bounce stuff off the moon? There's no gravity.
Comment faire rebondir un truc sur la lune sans la gravité ?
Oh, Leonard, this is Zack. Zack, Leonard.
Leonard, voici Zack. Zack, Leonard.
-Maybe another time. -Yeah. Maybe.
- Une autre fois. -Peut-être.
-Hey, I wanna see this laser thing. -Oh, what about the party?
- Moi, je veux voir le laser. - Et la fête ?
It's a surprise party, doesn't matter when we get there.
C‘est une surprise, peu importe quand on arrive.
Right.
Exact.
Okay, well, yeah, come on up.
Bon, d‘accord, montez.
LEONARD: So how'd you guys meet?
D'où vous vous connaissez ?
ZACK: My company designs the menus for The Cheesecake Factory.
Ma boite crée les menus de Ia Cheesecake Factory.
LEONARD: Your company?
Ta boite ?
ZACK: My dad, but me and my sister are VPs.
Celle de mon père. Je suis Vice-président.
LEONARD: So menus.
Alors, comme ça, des menus.
It sounds easy, but there's a lot of science that goes into designing them.
Ça semble simple mais la science yjoue un rôle important.
Happy now? I'm moving the dirty sock.
T'es content ? J'enlève la chaussette.
Thank you.
Merci.
Raj, keep an eye out for the other one.
Ra], continue à chercher l'autre.
-Hey, guys. This is my friend Zack. ZACK: Hey.
Salut, voici mon ami Zack.
Yes. In 1917...
Oui, en 1911,
...when Albert Einstein established the theoretic foundation for the laser...
quand Einstein a établi la théorie du laser
...in his paper Zur Quantentheorie der Strahlung...
dans Zur Quantentheorie des Strathng,
...his fondest hope was that the resultant device be "bitchen."
il fondait l'espoir que le résultat serait que "ça pète".
Well, mission accomplished.
Mission accomplie.
Let me explain what we're doing here.
Je t'explique ce qu'on fait.
In 1969, the astronauts on Apollo 11...
En 1969, les astronautes de Apollo 11
...positioned reflectors on the moon.
ont mis des réflecteurs sur la lune.
We're gonna shoot a laser off one of them...
On va envoyer un laser sur l'un d‘eux
...and let the light bounce back into this photomultiplier.
et la lumière rebondira dans ce photomultiplicateur.
Oh, that's very cool.
C‘est super cool.
One question: How can you be sure it won't blow up?
Une question : Comment être sûr que ça va pas exploser ?
-The laser? -The moon.
- Le laser ? - La lune.
See, now this is a man for Penny.
Ça, c‘est un homme pour Penny.
-That's a great question, Zack. -No, it's not.
- Excellente question, Zack. - Non, c‘est faux.
-Sheldon, play nice. -lt's not a great question.
- Sheldon, gentil. - Ce n‘est pas excellent.
How could somebody possibly think we're going to blow up the moon?
Comment croire qu'on va faire exploser la lune ?
That's a great question.
Ça. c‘est une excellente question.
Don't worry about the moon. We set our laser to stun.
Ne t'en fais pas pour la lune. On a fait ce qu'il faut.
We'll see the beam when it leaves.
On verra le rayon à son départ. Au retour, il ne sera pas assez puissant
-...to be seen by the naked eye. -Naked. Heh, heh, heh.
- pour qu'on le voit à l'œil nu. - Nu.
Right, funny.
C‘est marrant.
So that device there will measure the photons that return...
Cet appareil mesurera les photons qui reviendront
...and show it to us on this computer. Raj, get them some glasses.
et nous les retransmettra sur ce PC. Ra], lunettes.
Cool, it's gonna be in 3-D?
Génial, ce sera en 3-0 ?
Preparing to fire laser at the moon.
Prêts à faire feu.
SHELDON: Make it so.
C‘est parti.
There it is. There's the spike.
Voilà. Voilà la pointe.
Two-point-five seconds for the light to return. That's the moon. We hit the moon.
2,5 s pour que la lumière revienne. On a touché la lune.
That's your big experiment? All that for a line on the screen?
C‘est ça votre expérience ? Tout ça pour une ligne.
Yeah, but think about what this represents.
Oui, mais pense à ce que ça représente.
The fact that we can do this is the only way of definitively proving...
Le fait que ce soit faisable, prouve
...that there are man-made objects on the moon...
qu'il y a des objets humains sur la lune
...put there by a species that only 60 years before...
laissés par une espèce qui 60 ans plus tôt
...had just invented the airplane.
inventait seulement l'avion.
What species is that?
Quelle espèce ?
l was wrong. Penny can do better.
J'ai eu tort. Penny peut mieux faire.
-Okay, guys, thank you. It's been fun. -Yeah, thanks.
- Bon, merci les gars, c‘était sympa. - Merci.
-Should we invite them to the party? -No, just keep walking.
- On les invite àla fête ? - Non, marche.
He's must be very skilled at coitus.
Il doit exceller en matière de coit.
I'm telling you, dude...
Je te le dis,
...the only way to feel better about Penny going out with other guys...
pour oublier que Penny sort avec un mec,
...is for you to get back on the whores.
tu dois te remettre dans la putain.
-Horse. -What?
- Le bain. -Quoi ?
The phrase is "get back on the horse." Not whores.
L'expression c‘est : ”se remettre dans le bain."
That's disgusting, dude.
C‘est répugnant.
No, it's not.... Never mind.
Non, ce n‘est pas... Laisse tomber.
He is right, though.
Il a raison.
If you want, I can turn you on to this great new dating site I found.
J'ai dégoté un super site de rencontres, si tu veux.
No, thanks.
Non, merci.
You sure? They say they can find a match for anybody.
Ils trouvent quelqu'un à tous les coups.
-Have they found a match for you? -Tons.
- Ils t‘ont trouvé quelqu'un ? - Des tas.
I've had, like, eight dates in the last month.
J'ai eu 8 rencards en 1 mois.
Twelve, if you count the ones who showed up and left.
12 si tu comptes celles qui sont parties en me voyant.
-I can't bring the nitrogen tank down. -Why not?
- Je ne ramènerai pas l'azote. - Pourquoi ?
All right, let me restate that. It's very heavy and I don't want to.
Je reformule. C‘est lourd, etje ne veux pas le faire.
-l'll help you. -Thank you.
- Je vais t'aider. - Merci.
Lift with your knees, not your back.
Soulève avec tes genoux, pas ton dos.
Good night.
Bonne nuit.
You know what would be fun?
Tu sais ce qui serait drôle.
-Signing Sheldon up for online dating. -Yeah, right.
- Inscrire Sheldon sur le site. - C‘est ça.
No, think about it. We make it an experiment.
Ce serait une sorte d‘expérience.
Like when Frankenstein's monster was lonely and he found a wife.
Comme quand le monstre de Frankenstein a trouvé une femme.
He didn't find a wife.
Il n'en a pas trouvé.
They built him a wife out of dead body parts.
On lui en a fabriqué une avec des morceaux de corps.
Okay, we'll call that plan B.
Ça, ce serait le plan B.
Coming.
J‘arrive.
Damn you, you rat bastard.
Foutu salaud, va !
Are you drunk?
Tu es bourrée ?
Zack was a perfectly nice guy and then you ruined him.
Zack était parfait et tu as tout gâché.
How did I ruin him?
Comment ça ?
Because in the olden days, I never would've known he was so stupid.
Avant, je n'aurais jamais réalisé qu'il était bête.
-Come on, he wasn't that stupid. -Yes, he was.
- Il l‘était pas tant que ça. - Si.
He thought you were gonna blow up the moon.
Il croyait que vous alliez faire sauter la lune.
Okay, yeah, he's stupid. Heh, heh.
Oui, c‘est vrai qu'il est bête.
He spent the entire night...
Il a passé la soirée
...bragging about how he invented the word "appeteasers."
à se vanter d‘avoir inventé le mot ”amuse-bouffe."
How is that my fault?
Et ce serait ma faute ?
You have destroyed my ability to tolerate idiots.
Je n'arrive plus à tolérer les idiots.
Now, come with me.
Viens avec moi.
-Where are we going? -We're gonna have sex.
- Où va-t-on ? - On va faire l'amour.
LEONARD: Why? I mean, okay.
Pourquoi ? Je veux dire, d‘accord.
What's going on?
Qu'y a-t-il ?
Put on your noise-canceling headphones, because it's gonna get loud.
Bouche—toi les oreilles, ça va faire du bruit.
Ugh. Not this again.
Non, pas encore!
In what universe is this "low-pulp"?
”Pauvre en pulpe", n‘importe quoi!
Good morning, Penny.
Bonjour, Penny.
Do you have eyes in the back of your head?
Tu as des yeux derrière la tête ?
When one gets beaten up every other day in school...
Quand on se fait taper dessus àla récré,
...one, of necessity, develops a keen sense of hearing.
on développe, par nécessité, une oui‘e fine.
Incidentally, one can get beaten up in school...
D‘ailleurs, on peut se faire taper
...simply by referring to oneself as "one."
parce qu'on parle de soi àla 3e personne.
I'm making English muffins. Would you like an English muffin?
Je me fais des muffins. Tu en veux un ?
Oh, thanks, I'm not hungry.
Je n'ai pas faim. Merci.
FYI, my noise-canceling headphones proved ineffective last night.
Au fait, j'ai tout entendu cette nuit.
-Yeah, sorry about that. -As a native Texan, I must say...
- Navrée. - En tant que Texan,
...l've never heard the phrase "yeehaw" used in quite that context.
je n‘avais jamais entendu ”yahoo" dans ce contexte.
Oh, God.
Mon Dieu.
"Oh, God.ll
”Mon Dieu."
That I've heard on multiple occasions.
Ça par contre, je l'ai entendu.
In what universe is that "lightly toasted"?
”Légèrement grillé", n‘importe quoi!
This has to be the worst day of my life.
C‘est le pire jour de ma vie.
Good morning, Leonard.
Bonjour Leonard.
How many times have I asked you not to do that?
Je t'ai demandé de ne plus faire ça.
Counting this instance? Three hundred seventeen.
Oui, tu l'as fait 317 fois.
-Where's Penny? -She returned to her apartment.
- Où est Penny ? - Rentrée chez elle.
I presume to shower and vomit.
Pour se doucher et vomir.
Not necessarily in that order.
Pas forcément dans cet ordre.
Wonder why she didn't say goodbye.
Sans dire au revoir ?
Are you expecting me to offer an explanation of human behavior?
Tu t‘attends à une explication du comportement humain ?
I know. I thought as an outsider...
Je pensais qu'en tant qu‘exclus,
...you might be able to provide a fresh perspective.
tu m‘offrirais un point de vue extérieur.
Well, I have no difficulty believing you are not butter.
Je crois sans problème que tu n'es pas du beurre.
-I gotta run. Early shift. -Okay, I'll walk down with you.
- Je me sauve, je suis pressée. - Je fais un bout avec toi.
So last night was fun, huh?
C‘était sympa la nuit dernière.
PENNY: Yeah, it must've been. I just threw up in my closet.
Sûrement. Je Viens de vomir dans mon placard.
LEONARD: Bummer.
Mauvais trip.
l was thinking tonight maybe we could catch a movie.
On pourrait se faire un film ce soir.
Oh, yeah, tonight's not great for me.
Ça va pas le faire pour moi.
Doesn't have to be tonight. I'm free pretty much always.
Peut être un autre soir. Je suis tout le temps libre.
Leonard, last night was a mistake.
Leonard, c‘était une erreur.
When you say "mistake," do you mean a fortunate mistake...
Tu veux dire une heureuse erreur,
...like the discovery of penicillin?
comme la découverte dela pénicilline ?
Look, I'm sorry.
Je suis désolée.
l was drunk, I was lonely, I hated Zack.
J‘étais soûle etje me sentais seule.
Can we just forget it ever happened?
On pourraitjuste oublier ?
No, it's pretty well imprinted on my brain.
Non, mon cerveau l‘a plutôt bien imprimé.
Especially the whole rodeo thing.
En particulier le rodéo.
Oh, God.
Mon Dieu.
So that's it? Wham, bam, thank you, Leonard?
C‘est tout ? Pif, paf, merci Leonard ?
PENNY: Look, I said I'm sorry. Can't you please let it go?
J'ai dit que j‘étais désolée. Oublié.
How am I supposed to let it go? You used me for sex.
Et je fais comment ? Tu t'es servi de moi.
Morning, Mrs. Gunderson.
Bonjour, Mme Gunderson.
Good morning, Leonard. Or should I say "yeehaw"?
Bonjour, Leonard. Ou devrais-je dire ”yahoo" ?
-Holy crap. -What?
- Punaise. - Quoi ?
We finally have proof...
On a des preuves
-...that aliens walk among us. -Excuse me?
que des extraterrestres vivent parmi nous.
You're kidding. An actual woman?
Tu plaisantes. Une vraie femme ?
Yeah, look. Breasts and everything.
Oui, regarde. Des seins et tout ce qui va avec.
Trust me, breasts doesn't necessarily mean "woman."
Une paire de seins ne veut pas forcément dire femme.
-Since when? -l'll show you a picture...
- Depuis quand ? - Je te montrerai
...of my Uncle Louie in a bathing suit sometime.
une photo de mon oncle Louie.
Leonard, you gotta see this. We found a match for Sheldon.
Leonard, il faut que tu vois ça.
Great. Maybe she can have sex with him and walk out on him the next morning...
Elle pourra faire l‘amour avec et s'enfuir au matin
...without so much as a "How do you do?"
sans dire au revoir.
-Know what he's talking about? -No. Ask him.
- Il parle de quoi ? - Demande-lui.
-Leonard, what? -I don't wanna talk about it.
- Leonard ? - Je veux pas en parler.
That was a lousy suggestion.
C‘était une mauvaise idée.
Whatever.
Peu importe.
Right now, Dr. Sheldon Cooper has to send an e-mail to his perfect match.
A présent, le Dr Cooper doit envoyer un e-mail à sa moitié.
"Greetings, fellow life-form...."
“Salutations, chére semblable..."
If she can do it, I can do it.
Si elle peut le faire, je peux le faire.
I can't do it.
Je ne peux pas.
Hi, Leslie.
Salut, Leslie.
Leonard, what're you doing here?
Qu'est-ce que tu fais ici ?
I know. It's been a while.
Je sais, ça fait des lustres.
Yeah, 18 months.
Oui, 18 mois.
Right. Right.
C‘est ça, oui.
So how you doing?
Comment vas-tu ?
-Fine. You? -Not bad.
- Bien et toi ? - Pas mal.
You remember when we used to have sex...
Tu te souviens quand on faisait l‘amour
...and you said it didn't mean anything, it was just for fun?
et que tu disais qu'on ne faisait que s'amuser ?
[STAMMERING] Do you wanna do that again?
Ça te dit qu'on remette ça ?
What happened? Blondie dumped you?
La blondinette t‘a plaqué ?
She didn't dump me. We were just in different places in the relationship.
Elle ne m‘a pas plaqué. lncompatibilité géographique.
Right.
D‘accord.
Anyway, apparently, it's okay to go back to people you're no longer seeing...
Apparemment, on peut retrouver d‘anciennes connaissances
-...and have recreational sex with them. -Uh-huh.
et faire l‘amour pour s‘amuser.
So, what do you say?
Tu en dis quoi ?
Let me think about it.
Laisse—moi y réfléchir.
She's not coming back.
Elle ne reviendra pas.
Yes, but "him" doesn't even know about "her."
Mais ”lui" ne sait rien sur ”elle".
Well, "him" about to find out about "her."
Eh bien, ”lui" va découvrir son existence à ”elle".
Really? Us gonna tell him?
Vraiment? On va lui dire ?
SHELDON: Who's going to tell whom about what?
Qui va dire quoi à qui ?
Sheldon. Hey. Hi.
Sheldon. Salut.
Your surprise confuses me. I live here.
Votre surprise me trouble. Je vis ici.
Right.
C‘est vrai.
So, listen, what are you doing tomorrow afternoon?
Tu fais quoi demain après-midi ?
-Be more specific. -Four-thirty.
- Sois plus précis. -16h30.
That's not afternoon. That's preevning.
Ça, c‘est la pré—soirée.
-What? -lt's a time of day l invented.
- Quoi ? - J'ai inventé ce concept.
It better defines the ambiguous period...
Ça défini mieux ce moment ambiguë
...between afternoon and evening: preevning.
entre l'après-midi et le soir : Ia pré—soirée.
Fairly certain it will catch on as it fills a desperate need.
Ça va prendre, c‘est sûr, il y a un réel besoin.
Right, okay. What are you doing tomorrow preevning?
Bon. Tu fais quoi demain en pré-soirée ?
Well, tomorrow's Saturday. Saturday night is laundry night.
On sera samedi. Samedi soir, c‘est soirée-lessive.
So I'll be spending the preevning pre-sorting and pre-soaking.
Je passerai ma pré-soirée à pré—trier et à pré-tremper.
Okay, what if I were to tell you...
Et si je te disais
...tomorrow at 4:30, you could meet a woman...
que tu pourrais rencontrer une femme
...who has been scientifically chosen to be your perfect mate?
qui a scientifiquement été choisie pour être ta moitié.
I would snort in derision and throw my arms in the air...
Je grognerais etje léverais les bras au ciel,
...exhausted by your constant tomfoolery.
exaspéré par vos bêtises incessantes.
But it's true.
Mais c‘est la Vérité.
We put all your vital information into this dating site...
On a rentré tes informations sur le site,
...answered all questions like you would and they found a match for you.
on a répondu pour toi aux questions et ils ont trouvé.
-Her name is Amy Farrah Fowler. -Please.
- Elle s‘appelle Amy Farrah Fowler. - S'il vous plaît.
Even assuming you could answer any question the way I would...
Même si vous aviez répondu comme moi aux questions,
...the algorithms used by matchmaking sites are complete hokum.
les calculs utilisés sont des balivernes.
That's the answer we gave to the question.
C‘est ce qu'on a répondu.
"What is your attitude towards online dating?"
“Que pensez-vous de ce genre de site ?"
Well, Howard wanted to write "mumbo jumbo," but I said no.
Howard voulait écrire "baratin", mais j'ai dit non.
Our Sheldon would say "hokum."
Notre Sheldon dirait ”balivernes".
Come on, where's your scientific curiosity?
Et ta curiosité scientifique alors ?
Most of it is being applied to unraveling secrets of universe...
Elle sert à ne pas révéler les secrets de l‘univers
...while the rest of it is wondering why I'm having this conversation with you.
et une partie se demande pourquoi j'ai cette conversation.
Okay, how about this?
Voyons voir.
Even Spock had a date once every seven years.
Même Spock avait un rencard une fois tous les 7 ans.
He didn't date. It was pon farr.
C‘était le pon farr.
His blood boiled with mating lust.
Son sang bouillait, il devait s'accoupler.
Why don't you start with a cup of coffee...
Commence par un café
...and you can pon farr Amy Farrah Fowler later.
et tu pourras pon farrer Amy Farrah plus tard.
-I don't drink coffee. -All right, you can have a hot chocolate.
- Je ne bois pas de café. - Un chocolat alors.
As I will not be engaging in this nonsense, my choice of beverage is moot.
Puisqu'il ne se passera rien, pas la peine de parler boisson.
For the record, I only drink hot chocolate...
Mais pour info, je ne bois du chocolat
...in months with an R in them.
que les mois avec un R.
-Why? -What's life without whimsy?
- Pourquoi ? - Un peu de fantaisie, non ?
Okay, I'm out.
Allez, ça suffit.
Sheldon...
Sheldon,
...l've hidden the dirty sock from the roof somewhere in your apartment.
j'ai caché la chaussette sale quelque part ici.
Unless you're willing to come with us to meet this girl...
Si tu refuses le rendez—vous,
...it will remain there forever.
elle restera ici, pour toujours.
You're bluffing.
Tu bluffes.
Are you willing to risk it?
Tu prends le risque ?
Curse you.
Je te maudis.
Thirty feet.
9 mètres.
Oh. Hey, Leonard.
Salut, Leonard.
l was a perfectly happy, geeky, little lonely guy...
Avant, j‘étais un geek solitaire, parfaitement heureux
...and then you ruined me.
et tu es venue tout gâcher.
Are you drunk?
Tu es bourré ?
Come on. We're gonna have sex and it's not gonna mean a thing.
Viens, faisons l'amour, ça ne voudra rien dire.
PENNY: Are you out of your mind?
Tu as perdu la tête ?
I'm really starting to think there's a double standard here.
Ça fait vraiment deux poids deux mesures.
In a few minutes, when l gloat over the failure of this enterprise...
Lorsque je ricanerai face à l‘échec de cette entreprise,
...how would you prefer I do it? The standard "I told you so"?
vous préférerez entendre : “Je vous l'avez bien dit ?"
With a classic "neener-neener"?
Avec un classique:
Orjust my normal look of haughty derision?
Ou avec mon regard habituel de dérision hautaine ?
-You don't know we're wrong yet. -Haughty derision it is.
- Tu ne sais pas si on a tort. - Dérision hautaine.
Excuse me. I'm Amy Farrah Fowler. You're Sheldon Cooper.
Pardon. Je suis Amy Farrah Fowler. Vous êtes Sheldon Cooper.
Hello, Amy Farrah Fowler.
Bonjour, Amy Farrah Fowler.
I'm sorry to inform you that you have been taken in...
Navré de vous informer que vous avez été roulée
...by unsupportable mathematics...
par d'intolérables calculs,
...designed to prey on the gullible and the lonely.
dont le dessin est d'accabler Ie naif.
Additionally, I'm being blackmailed with a hidden dirty sock.
De plus, je suis sujet à un chantage àla chaussette sale.
If that was slang, I'm unfamiliar with it.
Si c‘est de l'argot, cela m‘est inconnu.
If it was literal, I share your aversion to soiled hosiery.
Dans le cas contraire, je partage votre dégoût.
I'm here because my mother and l have agreed that I will date at least once a year.
Ma mère souhaite que j'ai un rendez-vous 1 fois par an.
Interesting.
Intéressant.
My mother and l have the same agreement about church.
Ma mère et moi avons le même accord concernant l‘église.
I don't object to the concept of a deity, but I'm baffled by the notion...
Je n'ai rien contre le concept de foi mais je suis perplexe
...of one that takes attendance.
quant à la notion de pratique.
Well, then you might want to avoid East Texas.
Vous devriez alors éviter le Texas.
Noted. Now, before this goes any further, you should know...
Bien noté. Avant que cela n'aille plus loin,
...that all forms of physical contact...
vous devriez savoir que tout contact, y compris coital est exclus.
May I buy you a beverage?
Je peux vous offrir une boisson ?
Tepid water, please.
Eau tiède, merci.
Good God, what have we done?
Seigneur, qu'avons-nous fait ?
[ENGLISH - US - SDH]
[FRENCH]